Guide to the Sports Information Office: Photographic Negatives collection, circa 1924-1992, 1995, undated UA.13.02.0018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Football Negatives, circa 1924-1992; 1995; undated; 8
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 28
    - Phipps, Roy, 1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05432)
    - Piasecky, Alex, 1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05433)
    - Piasecky, Alex, 1941 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02739)
    - Pieczynski, Eddie, 1972 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02740)
    - Pieczynski, Eddie, 1972 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02741)
    - Pierson, Marty (Assistant Coach), 1965 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02742)
    - Pierson, Marty (Assistant Coach), 1965 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02743)
    - Pingitore, Abbie, 1952 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02744)
    - Pingitore, Joe, 1944 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02745)
    - Pinkston, Dutch, 1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05434)
    - Pitt, Howie, 1953 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02746)
    - Plaster, Claude "Nig," 1931, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05435)
    - Pless, John, 1955 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02747)
    - Plyler, [Marion, Jr. ?], 1929, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05436)
    - Politan, Joe, 1970 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02748)
    - Politan, Joe, 1971 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02749)
    - Politan, Joe, 1972 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02750)
    - Pollier, Fred, 1961 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02751)
    - Poole, Jake (with Bob Nanni), 1942, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05437)
    - Poole, Jake, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05438)
    - Poole, Steve, 1971 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02752)
    - Poole, Steve, 1972 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02753)
    - Poor, John, 1981 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02754)
    - Porreca, Nick, 1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05439)
    - Porterfield, David, 1940, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05440)
    - Poss, Summie, 1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05441)
    - Post, Ed, 1953-1955 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02755)
    - Potts, Charles "Zo," 1960-1962 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02756)
    - Powell, Johnny, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05442)
    - Powell, Larry, 1956 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02757)
    - Power, Tom, 1935, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05443)
    - Powers, Tom, 1949, 1950 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02758)
    - Prentis, Rick (Manager), 1966 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02759)
    - Preston, Pat, 1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05444)
    - Preston, Stan, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02760)
    - Price, Ted (Manager), 1939 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02761)
    - Price, Zac, 1979 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02762)
    - Price, Zac, 1980 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02763)
    - Price, Zac, 1981 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02764)
    - Pritchard, Greg, 1977 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02765)
    - Pritchard, Greg, 1978 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02766)
    - Pritchard, Greg, 1979 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02767)
    - Prosak, Barry, 1972 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02768)
    - Prosak, Barry, 1973 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02769)
    - Prothro, Tommy, 1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05445)
    - Prothro, Tommy, 1941 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02770)
    - Prothro, Tommy (color), 1941 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02771)
    - Pruitt, Bob, 1975 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02772)
    - Pruitt, Bob, 1976 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02773)
    - Pruitt, Bob, 1976 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02774)
    - Pruitt, Bob, 1977 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02775)
    - Pugh, David, 1968, undated (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02776)
    - Pugh, David, 1969 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02777)
    - Pugh, David, 1970 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02778)
    - Pugh, David (with Leo Hart), 1968 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02779)
    - Pyle, Bob, 1948 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02780)
    - Quinn, Ned, 1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05446)
    - Raether, Harold, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05447)
    - Raether, Harold, 1944 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02781)
    - Rainer, Mark "Red," 1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05448)
    - Rambo, Warren, 1950 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02782)
    - Ramey, Dale, 1961 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02783)
    - Ramey, Dale, 1961 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02784)
    - Ramsey, Barry, 1960-1962 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02785)
    - Ranson, Jim, 1978 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02786)
    - Rapp, Jim, 1972 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02787)
    - Rappold, Walt, 1958-1962 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02788)
    - Rappold, Walt, 1958-1962 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02789)
    - Raspberry, Jack, 1967 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02790)
    - Rawley, Curt, 1968 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02791)
    - Rawley, Curt, 1969 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02792)
    - Rawley, Curt, 1969 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02793)
    - Rawley, Curt, 1970 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02794)
    - Reagan, Phil, 1972 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02795)
    - Recinella, Bill, circa 1954-1956 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02796)
    - Recinella, Bill (with Coach Bob Cox), 1958 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02797)
    - Redding, Clyde, 1940-1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05449)
    - Redding, Clyde, 1940-1941 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02798)
    - Redding, Dick, 1972 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02799)
    - Redding, Dick, 1973 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02800)
    - Reese, John, 1946-1949, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05450)
    - Reese, John, 1946-1949 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02801)
    - Reese, Lee, 1965 (Box 22, Item UA13020018-N-02802)
    - Reider, Richard, 1965, 1966 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02803)
    - Reilly, Jim, 1975 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02804)
    - Reilly, Jim, 1976 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02805)
    - Reilly, Jim, 1977 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02806)
    - Renneker, Mike, 1965 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02807)
    - Renneker, Mike, 1966, 1967 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02808)
    - Renz, Harry, 1949 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02809)
    - Ressler, Mike, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05451)
    - Reynolds, Bill, 1958-1962 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02810)
    - Reynolds, Bill, 1958-1962 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02811)
    - Reynolds, Bruce, 1967 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02812)
    - Reynolds, John, 1961 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02813)
    - Rhett, Greg, 1977 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02814)
    - Rhett, Greg, 1977 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02815)
    - Rhett, Greg, 1978 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02816)
    - Rhinesmith, Mike, 1980 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02817)
    - Ribar, Frank, 1937-1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05452)
    - Ribar, Frank (with Bob Haas), 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05453)
    - Ricca, John, 1973 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02818)
    - Rice, Charles, 1949 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02819)
    - Richards, George, 1973 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02820)
    - Richardson, Dick, 1950 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02821)
    - Richardson, Terry, 1965, 1966 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02822)
    - Riesenfeld, Bob (with Pete Schafer), 1967 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02823)
    - Riggle, Gene, 1952 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02824)
    - Riggs, Mickey, 1952 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02825)
    - Riordan, Bob, 1977 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02826)
    - Riordan, Bob, 1978 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02827)
    - Riordan, Bob, 1979 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02828)
    - Ripple, Joel, 1964 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02829)
    - Ris, Howard (Manager), 1937, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05454)
    - Ritchie, Banks, circa 1955-1957 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02830)
    - Ritz, Mike (Trainer), 1976 Mar. (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02831)
    - Roane, Danny, 1958 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02832)
    - Robb, Spencer, 1937, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05455)
    - Robb, Spencer (with Bill Sally), 1937, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05456)
    - Robb, Spencer (with Carl Deane), 1937, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05457)
    - Robbins, Allen, 1954 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02833)
    - Robinson, Bill, 1949 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02834)
    - Robinson, Joe (Coach), 1971 Apr. (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02835)
    - Robinson, John, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05458)
    - Robinson, Roger (alone, with Willard Perdue), 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05459)
    - Robnett, Joe, 1945 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02836)
    - Rochelle, Pat, 1929, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05460)
    - Rogers, John, 1964-1965 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02837)
    - Rogers, John, 1964-1965 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02838)
    - Rogers, Lee, 1974 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02839)
    - Rogers, Lee, 1975 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02840)
    - Rogers, Lee, 1976 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02841)
    - Rogers, Tom, circa 1935, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05461)
    - Rojas, Fred, 1967, 1969 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02842)
    - Rojas, Fred, 1970 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02843)
    - Rose, Danny, 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02844)
    - Rose, Marty, 1953-1955 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02845)
    - Rose, Russ, 1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05462)
    - Roser, Vince, 1972 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02846)
    - Roser, Vince, 1973 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02847)
    - Rosky, Marcus "Buzz" (alone, with Bob Hayes), circa 1928-1930, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05463)
    - Rosoff, Cary, 1974 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02848)
    - Rosoff, Cary, 1975 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02849)
    - Rosoff, Cary, 1976 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02850)
    - Rossell, Hank, 1974 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02851)
    - Rossell, Hank, 1975 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02852)
    - Rossell, Hank, 1976 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02853)
    - Rossiter, Harry, 1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05464)
    - Rowe, Art, 1949 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02854)
    - Rowe, Joe, 1978 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02855)
    - Rowe, Joe, 1979 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02856)
    - Rowe, Joe, 1980 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02857)
    - Royal, Peter, 1966 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02858)
    - Royall, Ted, circa 1955-1958 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02859)
    - Rudy, Oliver, circa 1954-1957 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02860)
    - Ruffa, Anthony, 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05465)
    - Ruffa, Anthony, 1939 Jan. 6, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05466)
    - Ruffa, Anthony, 1940, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05467)
    - Ruffa, Anthony (with Tom Maloney), 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05468)
    - Rupp, Charles, circa 1928-1930, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05469)
    - Rushton, Eddie, circa 1954-1957 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02861)
    - Russ, Taft, circa 1928-1929, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05470)
    - Russell, Al (with Bill Bailey), 1935, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05471)
    - Rute, Bobby, 1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05472)
    - Rute, Bobby, 1943 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02862)
    - Rute, Gary, 1968, 1969 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02863)
    - Rute, Gary, 1970 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02864)
    - Rutherford, Don, 1973 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02865)
    - Ruttenberg, David, 1964 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02866)
    - Ryan, Frank, 1965, 1966, 1967 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02867)
    - Ryan, Mike, 1981 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02868)
    - Sacrinty, Bo, 1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05473)
    - Sally, Bill (with John Woody), 1937, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05474)
    - Salomon, Colgate, 1978 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02869)
    - Salvato, Joe, 1971 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02870)
    - Sammis, Mark, 1971 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02871)
    - Sandefur, Glenn, 1974 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02872)
    - Sandefur, Glenn, 1975 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02873)
    - Sandefur, Glenn, 1976 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02874)
    - Sandusky, Mike, 1975 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02875)
    - Sandusky, Mike, 1977 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02876)
    - Sargent, Ed, 1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05475)
    - Satyshur, Dennis, 1969 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02877)
    - Satyshur, Dennis (with unidentified female), 1969 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02878)
    - Satyshur, Dennis, 1971 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02879)
    - Satyshur, Dennis, 1975, undated (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02880)
    - Schafer, Pete, 1967, 1968 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02881)
    - Schmit, Dave, 1973 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02882)
    - Schmit, Dave, 1974 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02883)
    - Schmit, Dave, 1975 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02884)
    - Schneck, Tyrel, 1973 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02885)
    - Schneck, Tyrel, 1975 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02886)
    - Schoenhoft, Andy, 1976 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02887)
    - Schoenhoft, Andy, 1977 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02888)
    - Schoenhoft, Andy, 1978 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02889)
    - Schoettmer, Mark, 1978 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02890)
    - Schoettmer, Mark, 1979 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02891)
    - Schoettmer, Mark, 1980 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02892)
    - Schoettmer, Steve, 1973 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02893)
    - Schoettmer, Steve, 1974 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02894)
    - Schoettmer, Steve, 1975 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02895)
    - Schoomaker, Fred, 1950 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02896)
    - Schoonover, Dick, 1978 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02897)
    - Schrider, Bill, 1948 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02898)
    - Schriever, Jack, 1940, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05476)
    - Scioscia, L. T., 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05477)
    - Sciulli, Joe, 1969 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02899)
    - Scott, Jim, circa 1962-1963 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02900)
    - Scott, Jim, 1964 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02901)
    - Scudduth, Bob, 1952 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02902)
    - Scudieri, Phil, circa 1954-1956 (Box 23, Item UA13020018-N-02903)
    - Scupine, Bill, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05478)
    - Searl, Richard, 1971 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02904)
    - Searl, Richard, 1971 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02905)
    - Self, Joe, 1949 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02906)
    - Sensibaugh, Rod, 1974 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02907)
    - Sensibaugh, Rod, 1975 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02908)
    - Sensibaugh, Rod, 1976 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02909)
    - Senter, Brad (Assistant Coach), 1982 Sept. (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02910)
    - Senter, Jimmy (with J. Berry), 1936 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02911)
    - Serravezza, William, 1965, 1966 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02912)
    - Sexton, Bryan, 1974 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02913)
    - Sexton, Bryan, 1975 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02914)
    - Sexton, Bryan, 1976 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02915)
    - Sherrill, Zander, 1949, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05479)
    - Sherrill, Zander, 1949 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02916)
    - Shasby, Douglas, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02917)
    - Shasby, Douglas, 1966 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02918)
    - Sharpe, Luke, circa 1963-1965 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02919)
    - Sharkey, Ed, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05480)
    - Shannon, Don, 1972 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02920)
    - Shannon, Don, 1973 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02921)
    - Shankweiler, Fred, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05481)
    - Shackford, Hilliard, 1963-1965 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02922)
    - Shinn, Robert, 1968 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02923)
    - Shinn, Robert, 1969 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02924)
    - Shinn, Robert, 1970 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02925)
    - Short, Randy, 1968 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02926)
    - Short, Randy, 1969 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02927)
    - Shuford, Tommy, 1964 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02928)
    - Siegfried, Winston, circa 1939, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05482)
    - Siler, Leon, 1953 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02929)
    - Silk, Bob, 1948 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02930)
    - Sime, Dave, 1958 Oct. (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02931)
    - Sime, Dave, 1959 Sept. (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02932)
    - Simon, Steve, circa 1962-1964 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02933)
    - Simpson, Bill (Manager), 1957 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02934)
    - Simpson, Bill, circa 1962-1963 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02935)
    - Simpson, Bill, 1964 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02936)
    - Simpson, Frank, 1967 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02937)
    - Simpson, John (Freshman team), 1937, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05483)
    - Singer, Phil, 1968 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02938)
    - Sington, Fred, 1932-1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05484)
    - Sink, Fred, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05485)
    - Sink, Fred, 1944 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02939)
    - Sink, Joe, circa 1930-1932, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05486)
    - Sink, Joe, circa 1955-1957 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02940)
    - Sinkovitz, Frank, 1946, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05487)
    - Sinkovitz, Frank, 1946 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02941)
    - Skipworth, George, 1949, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05488)
    - Skipworth, George, 1949 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02942)
    - Skodzinski, Jules, 1954 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02943)
    - Slade, Troy, 1974 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02944)
    - Slade, Troy, 1974 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02945)
    - Slade, Troy, 1975 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02946)
    - Slade, Troy, 1975 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02947)
    - Small, Glenn, 1976 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02948)
    - Small, Glenn, 1977 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02949)
    - Small, Glenn, 1978 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02950)
    - Smathers, Faith, 1933, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05489)
    - Smathers, Pat, 1973 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02951)
    - Smathers, Pat, 1974 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02952)
    - Smathers, Pat, 1975 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02953)
    - Smider, Ted, 1972 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02954)
    - Smith, Andy, 1969, 1970 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02955)
    - Smith, Bill, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05490)
    - Smith, Bill, 1981 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02956)
    - Smith, Bob, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05491)
    - Smith, Charlie, 1950 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02957)
    - Smith, Charlie, 1971 Aug. (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02958)
    - Smith, Dana, 1961 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02959)
    - Smith, Gordon, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05492)
    - Smith, Harry, 1945, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05493)
    - Smith, Harwood, 1937, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05494)
    - Smith, Henry, circa 1947, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05495)
    - Smith, Herman, circa 1941-1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05496)
    - Smith, Herman, circa 1941-1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05497)
    - Smith, Herman, circa 1941-1943 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02960)
    - Smith, James, 1953 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02961)
    - Smith, Jerry, circa 1958-1960 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02962)
    - Smith, Jim, 1939, 1941, 1942 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02963)
    - Smith, Jim, 1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05498)
    - Smith, Lee, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05499)
    - Smith, Lyman, 1975 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02964)
    - Smith, Lyman, 1976 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02965)
    - Smith, Lyman, 1977 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02966)
    - Smith, Sherwood, 1973 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02967)
    - Smith, Walter, 1950 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02968)
    - Smith, [?] "Wimpy," 1974 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02969)
    - Smith, [?] "Wimpy," 1975 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02970)
    - Smith, [?] "Wimpy," 1976 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02971)
    - Snow, David, 1980 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02972)
    - Snow, David, 1981 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02973)
    - Snowberger, Don, circa 1952-1954 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02974)
    - Snyder, Bruce, 1972 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02975)
    - Snyder, Bruce, 1972 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02976)
    - Snyder, Bruce, 1973 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02977)
    - Snyder, Bruce, 1974 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02978)
    - Snyder, Bruce, 1974 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02979)
    - Snyder, Thoburn "Doc," 1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05500)
    - Sobocinski, Bob, circa 1955-1957 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02980)
    - Somers, Robert, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05501)
    - Somers, Robert, 1944 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02981)
    - Sommers, Dick, 1950 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02982)
    - Sommers, Rick, 1977 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02983)
    - Sommers, Rick, 1978 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02984)
    - Sorrell, Sonny, 1953-1955 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02985)
    - Sorrell, Sonny (with Buddy Bass), 1955 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02986)
    - Souchak, Mike, 1949, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05502)
    - Souchak, Mike, 1949 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02987)
    - Southerland, [?] (alone, with Ed Jontos), 1943, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05503)
    - Spada, Bob, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02988)
    - Spada, Bob, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02989)
    - Spangler, Bob, 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05504)
    - Spangler, Bob (with Don Hill, with Jeanette Bagwell), 1938, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05505)
    - Speacht, Gene, 1942-1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05506)
    - Spears, Hal, 1973 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02990)
    - Spears, Hal, 1973 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02991)
    - Spears, Hal, 1974 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02992)
    - Spears, Hal, 1974 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02993)
    - Spears, Hal, 1975 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02994)
    - Spears, Lee, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05507)
    - Spears, Lee, 1944 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02995)
    - Speas, Herb, circa 1941, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05508)
    - Spiers, Jon, 1981 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02996)
    - Spoganetz, John, 1971 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02997)
    - Spoganetz, John, 1972 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02998)
    - Sprye, Walter (Freshman team), 1936, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05509)
    - Spurrier, Steve (Coach, in Tampa, copy negative), 1983 Apr. (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-02999)
    - Staley, Don, 1971 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03000)
    - Stallings, Riley, 1954 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03001)
    - Stanier, Chuck, 1960 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03002)
    - Stanley, Buddy, circa 1953-1955 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03003)
    - Stanley, Dutch (Coach, with Wallace Wade), 1939 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03004)
    - Stanley, Dutch (Coach), 1941, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05510)
    - Starrett, Randy, 1962 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03005)
    - Staudinger, Ken, 1976 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03006)
    - Staudinger, Ken, 1977 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03007)
    - Staudinger, Ken, 1978 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03008)
    - Stavins, Charles, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03009)
    - Stavins, Charles, 1966 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03010)
    - Steel, Howard, 1958 May (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03011)
    - Stene, Hugh, 1948, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05511)
    - Stene, Hugh, 1948 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03012)
    - Stephanz, Paul, 1944, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05512)
    - Stephanz, Paul, 1949, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05513)
    - Stephanz, Paul, 1949 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03013)
    - Stephen, Ronnie (Head Manager), 1963 (Box 24, Item UA13020018-N-03014)
    - Stephens, Hal "Ducky," 1935, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05514)
    - Stephens, Hal "Ducky," 1937-1938, undated, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05515)
    - Stephens, Hal "Ducky" (with Porter Greenwood, in the library), 1937, Nitrate (Box 38, Item UA13020018-N-05516)